centercutcook.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy - CenterCutCook

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@centercutcook.com.

At CenterCutCook, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by CenterCutCook and how it is used. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from April 22, 2015.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, CenterCutCook makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Email

We will not give or sell your email address to anyone. You can [unsubscribe](https://www.centercutcook.com/email-subscription/?action=unsubscribe) from the daily emails at any time, and the changes will take effect immediately. If you have any issues or complaints regarding the emails please do not hesitate to [contact us](https://www.centercutcook.com/contact/).

## Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

## Opt-Out of Cookies

You can opt-out of cookies using the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

## What We Collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CenterCutCook.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to CenterCutCook and other sites on the Internet.
  * [Users may opt out](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Amazon, Tribal Fusion, Gourmet Ads, and Sovrn.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on CenterCutCook send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. CenterCutCook has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. CenterCutCook’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Google Analytics

CenterCutCook uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to better understand who visits our site. Google has developed the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to enable website visitors opt-out from get their data from the website visit collected by Google Analytics. You can also use [Google’s Ads Settings.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)
